안녕
Hi
안녕!
Hey / Hi
돌아왔구나~
Look who is back?
신혼여행 어땠어?
How is the honeymoon?
최고였어!
oh, incredible!
Oh, champagne, candle-lit dinners, moonlight walks on the beach were so romantic.
샴페인도 마시고 낭만적인 저녁식사에다
달빛 아래 해변도 거닐고...
너무 로맨틱했어
그래 마이크는?
So where is Mike?
병원에 갔어
He is with doctor.
거기 있는 동안 화장실
한번도 안갔거든
He didn't poop the whole time over there.
어쨌거나, 정말 잘 돌아왔다
나 네 도움이 필요하걸랑
Well, anyway, I'm glad you're back.
I really need your help.
Oh, why? What's up?
무슨 일인데?
나 연극 오디션이 있는데
거기서 불어를 써야 돼
Well, I have an audition for this play, and for some of it, I had to speak french.
Which, according to my resume, I'm fluent in.
내 이력서에는
내가 유창하다고 써있거든
조이, 이력서에 거짓말 쓰면 안돼
Joey, you shouldn't lie on your resume.
그럼, 안돼고 말고
Yeah, you really shouldn't.
근데 말이지, 오빠 1년 동안
카이로에서 탐사했던 건 어땠어?
By the way, how was that year long dig in cairo?
괜찮았어
It was okay.
너 불어하는 지 몰랐는 걸?
I did not know you spoke French.
Oui, bien sur je parle francais.
oh. You're so sexy.
너 진짜 섹시하다
도와줄거지?
나 이 연극 진짜 하고 싶단 말야
So will you help me?
I really want to be in this play.
물론이지
Sure!
Tous les plaisirs est pour moi, mon ami.
그만 그만
나 너 덮쳐버릴지도 몰라
seriously, stop it or
I'm gonna jump on you.
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
10x13 The One Where Joey Speaks French
[제 작]
코리아닷컴 프렌즈동호회 자막팀
[번 역]
단형철(divine0422@korea.com)
[제 작]
코리아닷컴 프렌즈동호회 자막팀
[테스터]
오종현(hiro97@korea.com)
[번 역]
단형철(divine0422@korea.com)
[싱 커]
김윤현(dbsgus99@korea.com)
[테스터]
오종현(hiro97@korea.com)
임의 수정 및 상업적용도의 사용을 금합니다
수정사항은 피드백 게시판에 남겨주세요 (club.korea.com/friends)
[싱 커]
김윤현(dbsgus99@korea.com)
임의 수정 및 상업적용도의 사용을 금합니다
수정사항은 피드백 게시판에 남겨주세요
(club.korea.com/friends)
Hey ! Why are you wearing my apron?
내 앞치마 두르고
뭐 하는 거야?
에리카 줄 쿠키 굽고 있어
I'm making cookies for Erica.
그리고 우리 곧 공항으로 가야 돼
한시간 뒤면 비행기 도착할 거야
By the way, we have to leave for the airport soon.
Her plane comes in in about an hour.
에리카 오면 말이지
내가 애들한테 이렇게 소개해도 될까?
Oh, hey, when she gets here, is it okay if I introduce you two
as my wife, and the woman who's carrying my child?
'내 아내랑 내 애를 밴 여자야'
안될까?
No?
이혼 생각하는 거 아니지?
Divorce?
안녕
Hey.
혹시 레이첼 봤어?
You guys know where Rachel is?
아니, 아침 이후로 못 봤는데
I haven't seen her since this morning.
말도 안돼, 30분 전에
에마 데리고 만나기로 했었단 말야
It's unbelievable. She was supposed to meet me a half hour ago with Emma.
안돼!
Hey.
왜 그래?
Hey!
이거 에리카 줄 거란 말야
These are for Erica.
이 많은 걸 혼자 다 먹는다고?
What, she's going to eat all those cookies?
난 아이가 태어났을 때
귀엽고 토실토실했음 좋겠다구
Well, I want the baby to come out all cute and fat.
그래, 근데 에리카가
왜 여기까지 오는데?
So why is Erica coming to visit?
그냥, 좀 더 친해지는 것도
좋을 것 같아서
Because we want to get to know her better,
and, uh... plus, she's never been to New York,
so she's wants to see all the tourist spots:
게다가 뉴욕에 한번도 와본 적 없으니까
여기저기 구경하고 싶을 거야
자유의 여신상이랑
엠파이어 스테이트 빌딩 같은 곳들
The statue of liberty and Empire state building...
those places, there's always so many people,
and they're being corralled like cattle.
그런 곳은 항상 사람들이 너무 많아
무슨 소떼 우리에 모아놓은 것 같잖아
게다가 거기서 꼭 음메~하는
바보 같은 놈들이 있다니까
And there's always some idiot who goes "moo."
그게 그렇게 듣기 싫으면
왜 계속 하는데?
Well, if it annoys you so much, then why do you do it?
안녕?
30분 뒤에 나타나줘서 고마워
Oh, hi. Hi.
Thanks for showing up 30 minutes late.
로스
Ross...
아니, 아냐, 됐어
물론 이유가 있겠지
no, no, no, I'm sure you have a great excuse. What was it, a hair appointment?
머리 셋팅이라든지 메이크업이라든지
아니면 바니스에서 세일이라도 하던?
A mani-pedi? Was there a sale at Barney's?
우리 아빠 심장 마비 일으켰어
My father had a heart attack...
나 바니스에서 쇼핑 중이었는데!
while I was at Barney's.
맙소사
Oh, my god.
어쩜
Honey...
I'm so sorry.
괜찮아?
Is he okay?
괜찮으시대?
응, 괜찮으실 거라고는 하는데
진정제로 안정시켜놓은 거잖아
Yeah, they said he's going to be fine,
but he's still heavily sedated.
내가 같이 롱아일랜드로 갈게
너 지금 혼자 있으면 안돼
Okay, okay, I'm going to come out to Long Island with you.
I mean, you can't be alone right now.
아니야, 나 괜찮아
No, come on, I'm totally okay.
너 올 필요 없대두
I don't need you to come.
절대 혼자 감당할 수 있어
I can totally handle this on my own.
그래두, 나 같이 가게 해줘
그래야 내가 안심하지
Still, still, let me come... for me.
그래, 그래야 네가 안심이 된다면
Okay, if you really need to.
모니카의 갓 구운 쿠키 먹으면
힘이 솟겠지?
I bet someone could use one of Monica's freshly baked cookies.
응, 정말 그럴 것 같아
Oh, I really could.
그래, 이거 간단해 뵈는데
All right, this seems pretty simple.
첫 대사는 '내 이름은 클라우드입니다'야
Your first line is, "my name is Claude."
So just repeat after me.
나 따라 읽어
Je m'appelle claude.
(-_-....Je de coup, plau.)
다시 한번 해보자
Well, let's just... let's try it again.
그래
Okay.
Je m'appelle claude.
Je de ple, mloo. -_-
Huh. It's not quite what I'm saying.
나랑 그다지 비슷하지 않은데?
정말? 나한테는 똑같이 들리는데
Really? Sounds exactly the same to me.
그래? 정말?
It does, really?
그렇대도
Yeah.
그래, 좋아
다시 해보지 뭐, 잘 들어
All right, let's just try it again.
Really listen.
알았어
Got it.
Je m'appelle claude.
Je da flup, flee. -_-
Oh, mon dieu.
Oh, de foof. -_-
안녕, 얘들아
Hey, you guys.
안녕
Hi.
Hi / Hey.
아주 특별한 사람 소개시켜줄게
I want you to meet someone really special.
피비, 이쪽은 에리카
그리고 여기는 아기
Phoebe, this is Erica.
And this is the baby.
Hi.
조이, 에리카, 아기
Joey... Erica. Baby.
안녕하세요
Hi.
모두들!
에리카랑 아기입니다!
Everyone... Erica. Baby.
모니카! 진정! 자신!
Monica. Calm. Self.
여기 앉으세요
Hey, sit down.
고마워요
만나게 돼서 정말 반가워요
There you go.
It's really nice to meet you guys.
여기 있다는 게 믿기질 않네요
I can't believe I'm here.
뉴욕에 오신 걸 환영해요
Welcome to New York city.
Or should I say...
gue de floof, New York city.
Why would you say that?
왜 그렇게 말하는데?
그래, 오늘 뭐 할 건가요?
Okay, what are you going to be doing today?
다 보고 싶어요
타임 스퀘어, 코니 아일랜드, 록펠러 센터
Well, I want to see everything:
Times Square, Coney Island, Rockefeller Center..
아! 자유의 여신상 꼭대기까지
걸어 올라가보는 것도 좋죠
Oh, you know what you should do?
You should walk all the way to the top of the Statue of Liberty.
그게 좋겠네요, 그렇게 해요
Oh, yeah, let's do that.
좋죠~
Great.
아이만 별로였단 봐라
This baby better be really good.
저기요, 저 아빠 뵈러 왔는데요
제 이름은 레이첼 그린이에요
Hi. Excuse me, I'm here to see my father.
My name is Rachel Green.
전 로스 겔러박사에요
And I'm Dr. Ross Geller.
로스, 여긴 병원이야
Ross, please, this is a hospital, okay.
박사란 말이 제대로
쓰이는 곳이라구
That actually means something here.
들어가도 될까요?
So can we please go in?
물론이죠
Absolutely.
난 여기서 기다릴게
Rach, I think I'm gonna wait out here because, uh...
나 목이 따끔거리는 게
혹시라도 병균 전염시키면 안되니까
my throat is feeling a little scratchy.
I don't want to infect him.
로스, 우리 아빠
너무 무서워하지 마
Ross, please,
don't be so scared of him.
무서워하는 게 아니라
진짜 아픈 것 같다니까
I'm not scared of him, I'm really sick.
진정제 맞고 지금은
의식이 없는 상태에요
He's under sedation,
so he's pretty much out.
좀 나은 것 같은데?
I'm feeling better.
oop
맙소사
oh, my god.
Oh. Oh, wow, that ear and nose hair trimmer I got him was just money down the drain, huh?
이런
귀랑 코털 정돈기 사준 건
완전히 돈 낭비였네
그린양, 아버님 담당 의사 선생님과
통화 가능한데요
Ms. Green, your father's doctor is on the phone if you'd like to speak to him.
잘 됐네요, 괜찮지?
Oh, great. Are you going to be okay?
He's unconscious.
I think we'll be just fine.
물론, 기절 중이시잖아
Okay.
um, did... did the TV wake you?
TV 소리가 너무 컸나요?
아니
No.
내 침대에 발 올리면서
내 도뇨관을 땡겼어
When you put your feet up on my bed, you tugged on my catheter.
아뿔사!
Ouchie.
여기서 뭐하는 건가, 겔러
What are you doing here, Geller?
레이첼이랑 같이 왔죠
고.. 곧 돌아올 거에요
I came with Rachel,
who should be back any second.
어떻게 지내세요?
So what's new?
Oh, I had a little heart attack.
쬐끄만 심장마비 하나 일으켰지
많이 고통스러운가요?
Right. Is it painful?
어떤 거, 심장마비?
아니면 지금 자네랑 얘기하는 거?
What, the heart attack,
or sitting here talking to you?
Let's see if we can get that Rachel back in here.
레이첼 부르죠
그래, 자넨 어떻게 지내나?
So what's new with you?
Knocked up any more of my daughters lately?
내 딸들 중 누구 다른 애
임신시키진 않았고?
아뇨, 레이첼이 다에요, 레이첼!
Nope. Just the one. Rach!
Je m'appelle claude.
Je dup kol, mlu.
아니야!
No !
좋아, 짧게 끊어서 해보자
Okay. Maybe if we just break it down.
한 음절씩 할 테니까 따라해 봐
Okay, let's just...
let's try it one syllable at a time.
Okay, so repeat after me.
Je / Je / M'A / M'A / Pelle / Pelle
그래, 그거야, 좀 더 빨리
Great. Okay, faster.
Je / Je / M'A / M'A / Pelle / Pelle
Je m'appelle./ Me poo poo.
Okay, it's too hard. I can't teach you.
너무 어려워
나 너 못가르치겠어
뭐 하는 거야?
What are you doing?
나 가야 돼
더 있다간 너 패겠다
I have to go
before I put your head through a wall.
안돼! 가지 마~
No, no! Don't go. I need you.
나 오디션 내일이란 말야!
My audition is tomorrow.
Ja blu bla! Me la pee! Oom blah! Poo.
Hey. / Hi.
저녁 준비하려고 그랬는데
I was going to make us some dinner,
but all I found in your dad's fridge was bacon and heavy cream.
냉장고에 베이컨이랑
크림 소스 밖에 없더라고
I think we solved the mystery of the heart attack.
심장마비 원인을 밝혀낸 듯 하네
너희 부모님한테 연락했어?
Did you call your parents?
응, 에마 잘 지내고 있다셔
Oh, yeah. Emma's doing great.
다행이다
Oh, good.
Wow.
왜?
What?
그냥, 레이첼 그린의
방에 있다는 게 안믿겨져서
Just can't believe I'm in Rachel Green's room.
무슨 소리야?
전에도 내 방에 와봤잖아
What do you mean?
You've been in my room before.
퍽이나 그랬겠다
Yeah, sure, right.
내가 레이첼 그린의 방에
잘도 와봤겠지
Like I'd ever be in Rachel Green's room.
내 이름 다 부르니까
되게 어색하다
Okay, I gotta tell you, it's really weird when you use my whole name.
미안
Sorry.
괜찮아?
You okay?
응
Yeah.
힘들었지?
You had a rough day, huh?
응, 아빠 그런 모습 보니까 이상해서
Yeah. Just so weird seeing him like that, you know?
I mean, he's a doctor.
You don't expect doctors to get sick.
의사가 그렇게 아플 거라고
누가 생각하겠어?
우리 박사들도 아프지
But we do.
You know, he's going to be okay, Rach.
괜찮으실 거야
Oh, I don't want him to wake up alone.
I should go to the hospital.
아빠 혼자 깨어나게하기 싫어
나 병원에 가있을래
No, no. Hey, hey, hey, look.
아니 아니, 내 말 들어봐
What?
병원에서 약을 많이 줘서
네가 옆에 있어도 모르실 거야
They gave him a lot of medication, okay?
He wouldn't even know if you were there.
이렇게 하자
아침에 눈뜨자마자 병원에 가보자
We'll go see him first thing in the morning, okay?
그래도 될까?
죄책감 안 느껴도 될까?
Really? I shouldn't feel guilty?
말도 안돼
레이첼, 넌 훌륭한 딸이야
No. Hey, Rach,
you've been an amazing daughter, okay?
지금 넌 휴식이 필요하다구
Right now you just need to get some rest.
Okay, maybe you're right.
그래, 네 말이 맞을 거야
잘 자
Good night.
잠깐
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
나랑 잠시만 같이 있어줄래?
Would you stay here with me for a little while?
그러지 뭐
Sure. Okay.
오늘 같이 와줘서 고마워
Thank you for coming with me today.
무슨 말이야
당연한 거지
Oh, of course.
레이첼 그린은 네가 그녀의
방에 있어서 아주 행복해
Rachel Green is very happy you're in her room.
나도야, 이리 와
Me, too. Come here.
오늘 밤은 혼자 있고 싶지 않아
I just don't want to be alone tonight.
그래 뭐, 침낭 같은 거
구해볼 수 있을 거야
Okay, well, um... I can maybe grab a sleeping bag or... oh... oh.
레이첼, 잠깐만!
No, Rach!
미안, 이건 좋은 생각이 아닌 것 같아
I'm sorry, I just...
I just don't think this...
this is a good idea.
해보기 전엔 모르잖아, 안그래?
Well, we won't know that until we do it, will we?
Uh, look, um, you are upset about your father and you're feeling vulnerable.
너 지금 아빠 일 때문에 당황해서 그래
불안하기도 하고
And I just don't feel it would be right.
I feel like I'd be, you know, taking advantage of you.
꼭 내가 기회 노리는 거 같잖아
Taking advantage?
I'm giving you the advantage. Enjoy.
기회를 노려? 난 지금 너한테
기회를 주는 거야, 놓치지 말라구!
Look, I'm sure it would be great.
But I think one of us has to be thinking clearly.
물론 좋겠지, 하지만 지금은 우리
둘 중 하나는 제정신일 필요가 있어
그러니까 나 이만 가볼게
So I'm going to go.
Wow. Okay.
그러던지
아침에 보자
I'll see you in the morning.
4개월째 혼자인데
이건 메달감이야!
Haven't had sex in four months.
I should get a medal for that.
이렇게 많은 곳들을 다 보여주시다니
고마워요, 너무 좋았어요
Thanks so much for taking me to all those places.
I had a great time.
Oh, I'm glad.
Listen, I want to apologize about Chandler, though. I just did not see this coming.
천만에요, 하지만
챈들러 일은 사과할게요
이러리라고는 상상도 못했어요
뉴욕 끝내준다!
New York is awesome!
너 왜 그래?
What is with you?
전에 다 가본 곳들인데
예전엔 제대로 못봤었어
You know, I've been to these places before,
but I've never really seen them, you know?
그래, 계속 '음메~'거리니까
제대로 못볼 만도 하지
Yeah, you miss a lot when you're mooing.
여기저기 데리고 다니시느라
수고하셨어요
Thanks so much for showing me around.
Oh, it was our pleasure.
We're so much enjoying getting to know you.
아니에요, 우리도 좋았어요
서로 더 알게 돼서 더 기쁘구요
Well, if there's anything else you want to know...
뭐 더 궁금하신 거 있으세요?
oh. Uh... okay.
그럼...
Um, do you mind if we ask you some questions about the father?
혹시 아이 아빠에 대해
알 수 있을까요?
Oh, sure. Yeah.
예, 물론이죠
제 고등학교 남자친구였어요
Well, he was my high school boyfriend.
풋볼팀 주장에다가
아주 멋진 애였죠
Captain of the football team. Really cute.
장학금 받고 대학에 갔어요
And he got a scholarship and went off to college.
대단하네요
That's great.
예... 아마도 거의 확실히
걔가 아이 아빠일 거에요
Yeah, it's almost definitely him..
그게 무슨 말이죠?
How's that now?
Well, there's a chance it's another guy.
다른 사람일 수도 있어요
I mean, I've only ever been with two guys, but they sort of overlapped.
남자친구는 둘 뿐이었지만
기간이 좀 겹쳐서요
그럼 그 다른 친구는 뭐하는데요?
그 친구도 대학 다니나요?
So what does the other guy do?
Does he go to college, too?
아뇨, 감옥에 있어요
No, he's in prison.
Oh. Was he falsely accused of something?
잘못 잡혀들어갔나요?
No,
아니요
아버지를 삽으로 쳐서 죽였어요
he killed his father with a shovel.
그것만 빼면 정말 괜찮은 애에요
But other than that, he's a great guy.
그 아버지는 그렇게 생각 안할걸요
I'll bet his dad doesn't think so.
깨어있어?
Are you awake?
당연히 깨어있지
앞으로는 항상 깨어있을 거야
Of course I'm awake!
Assume from now on that I'm always awake!
그 사람인지 아닌지는 모르는거잖아
풋볼팀 주장이었던 애일 수도 있잖아
All right. We don't know that it's him. I mean, it could be the football guy.
Honey, it's us!
Of course it's the shovel killer!
다른 사람도 아니고 우리 얘기야
당연히 삽 살인마가 아빠지
그래, 좋아
그 사람이라고 쳐
All right, let's say that it is him.
그렇다고 우리가 아이를
원하지 않을거야? 아니잖아
Would we not want the baby? No.
아이를 다르게 대할 거야?
Would you treat him any differently?
예의주시하겠지!
I'd keep an eye on him!
아이 아빠가 누군지 알아내야 돼
We have to find out which one the father is.
어떻게?
How?
나도 모르지
이런 것 찾아주는 사람 있잖아?
I don't know.
They have tests for these things, right?
그래, 하지만 우리가
너무 오버하는 거 아냐?
Yeah, but maybe we're just overreacting.
Easy for you to say.
He's a father killer.
넌 걱정 없겠지
그 인간은 아버지 살인마잖아
아마 어머니는 사랑하겠지
He probably loves his mommy.
삽 휘두르는 팔에
'엄마'라고 문신 새겼을 거다
He's probably got a tattoo then says "mom" on his shovel-wielding arm.
1부터 5까지 세봅시다
We'll now count from one to five.
Un, deux, trois, quatre, cinq.
Enh, bluh, blah, fluh, flank.
참 잘했어요
Good job.
감사합니다~
Thank you.
안녕, 조이
어제 일은 정말 미안해
Hey. Hey, Joey.
Listen, I feel really badly about yesterday.
생각을 좀 해봤는데
내가 너무 인내력이 부족했어
And I thought about it a lot.
I was too impatient.
다시 시도해보자
So let's try it again.
No, that's okay. I don't need your help.
I worked on it myself.
And I gotta say I am pretty good.
아니야 됐어, 혼자 연습해봤는데
꽤 잘하는 것 같어
Really? Can I hear some of it?
정말? 좀 들려줘봐
물론이지
Sure, sure.
Okay.
blay de la blay de blu blah blay!
어때?
See?
너... 너 아직. 여전히...
You're not... you're not... again,
그건 불어가 아니야!!
you're not speaking french!
Oh, well, I think I am!
Yeah. And I think I'm definitely going to get the part.
내 생각엔 맞는 거 같은데?
오디션에도 붙을 거야!
어떻게 그렇게 생각해?
How could you possibly think that?
적어도 테잎에 있는 사람은
나 참 잘한댔다구!
For one thing, the guy on the tape said I was doing a good job!
나도 한잔 줄래?
Hey, Rach, could you grab me a cup of coffee?
그래
Sure.
아침 내내 조용하던데, 괜찮아?
You've been quiet all morning.
Is everything okay?
Mm-hmm.
응
정말 괜찮지?
You sure you're all right?
그래!
Yep.
그래, 나 가서 아침 좀 사올게
OKy.
Um, well, I'm going to go grab us some breakfast.
참고로 말해두자면~
FYI... (For Your Information)
그럼 그렇지
There it is.
앞으로 어떤 여자가 경솔하고
동정심에 호소하며 섹스를 원하면
In the future, when a girl asks for some ill-advised sympathy sex,
그냥 해줘
just do it.
Wait, wait.
You're mad at me about last night?
잠깐, 지금 어젯밤 일 때문에
나한테 화가 난 거야?
난 그저 옳은 일을 한 것 뿐이야
I was just trying to do the right thing.
정말? 만약에 네가
옳은 일을 한 거였다면
Really? Well, it seems to me if you'd done the right thing,
I would not have woken up today feeling stupid and embarrassed.
내가 아침에 일어나면서
바보 같거나 창피하지 않고
I would have woken up feeling comforted and satisfied.
마음이 편하고 흡족한 상태로 깼겠지
그야 물론...
Well...
그만 둬
oh, stop that!
어이가 없네
난 그저 옳은 일을 했을 뿐이라구
I can't believe this.
What do you... I... I was just being a good guy.
널 존중하고 이해심으로 대한 거라구
I treated you with respect and understanding.
어쩜, 너무 멋지네
Oh, that's so hot.
Hey, I was looking out for you!
다 널 위해서였다구
Oh, really?
Well, Ross, you know what?
I am a big girl.
그래? 난 다 컸다구
좋다 나쁘다 나한테
말해줄 사람 필요 없어
I don't need someone telling me what is best for me.
섹스 못하게 된 적은 많았지만
이번이 최악이네
I got to say I've not had sex a lot of times before. This is the worst ever.
Oh, really? Really?
Well, it wasn't very good for me, either.
그래? 그래?
나도 꽤나 별로였어
Oh, okay.
Hey, hey, you know what?
You know what?
그래?
그럼 이건 어때?
앞으로도 이런 상황
안생기게 하기 위해서
To avoid this little thing in the future,
let's just say--you and me?
Never having sex again.
너랑 나 이제
절대 같이 자지 않기다
뭐?
What?
그래! 섹스는 이제 물 건너갔어
That's right. Sex is off the table.
난 다시는 너랑 안해
I am never having sex with you again.
그린 박사님
좀 괜찮아지셨나요?
Dr. Green, are you feeling better?
어서 와요
점심은 어땠어요?
Hey.
How was lunch?
We had a good time. By the way,
I wanted to ask you something.
재미있었어요, 그런데요
저 꼭 하나 물어볼 게 있어요
It would really mean a lot to me--
if the baby was a boy-- that you name him after my father,
만약 아이가 아들이라면
아빠 이름을 땄으면 좋겠어요
지미나 빌리 밥
Jiminy billy bob.
Oh, really ?
정말요?
아니에요~
이거 정말 재미있네요
No! You were right. That was fun.
전 가서 짐 마저 쌀 게요
I'm going to go finish packing.
그래요
Okay.
그래서 검사 받아보기로 했어?
So, is she going to take the test?
아니, 그럴 필요 없게 됐어
Nope. She doesn't have to.
내가 아이 아빠
누군지 알아냈으니까
I found out who the father is.
이런...
'삽 스윙맨'이지?
Oh, god. It's shovely joe, isn't it?
아니야
No, it's not.
How do you know?
어떻게 알아?
에리카가 성교육 시간에
집중을 안했나봐
Well, it turns out that Erica didn't pay much attention in sex ed class
감옥에 있는 친구랑 했던 식으로는
아이 갖기가 힘들지
'cause the thing she did with that prison guy?
It'd be pretty hard to make a baby that way.
그래? 어떤 식이길래
Oh, god, what was it?
The thing we hardly ever do,
or the thing we never do?
우리가 거의 안하는 거야
아님 우리가 절대 안하는 거?
절대 안 하는 거
The thing we never do.
요~ 삽 스윙 맨~
Shovely joe.
준비되는 대로 시작해요, 조이
Whenever you're ready, Joey.
알았어요
Right.
Jai boo boo, claude. Uh, sle poo. Laylu blah blu.
뭐라는 거에요?
I'm sorry. What's going on?
이봐요, 불어를 써야죠
Dude, come on. French it up.
조이, 불어 할 줄 알아요?
Joey, do you speak French?
Toot de la smor!
Blu, blu ay, blu blah. Foo...
오디션 끝내도 되겠네요
you know what?
I think this audition is over.
Excuse me.
잠시만요
제 이름은 루진 필란쥐인데요
I am Regine Filange.
I was passing by when I heard this man speaking
the, the regional dialect of my French town of estee lauder.
지나다가 이 분이 제 고향인 에스테로더
지방의 방언을 하는 걸 듣고 들어왔어요
지금 이 사람이 진짜 불어를
한다고 생각하는 거에요?
You really think this man is speaking french?
Oh, sa sa!
잠시만요, 실은
이 사람은 제 동생이에요
Ecoutez, je vais vous dire la verite. [Okay, I'll tell you the truth.]
C'est mon petit frere. Il est... un peu retarde.
[He's my little brother. He's a little retarded.]
약간... 모자라요
그냥 맞장구 쳐주심 안될까요?
Alors, si vous pouviez jouer le jeu avec lui?
[Would you please just humor him?]
참 잘 했어요
Good job, little buddy.
불어가 유창하네요
That was some really good French.
하지만 이 배역에는
다른 사람을 써야할 것 같네요
But I think we're going to go with someone else for the part.
Oh. All right.
But my french was good?
그래요
하지만 제 불어는 괜찮았죠?
훌륭했어요
It was great.
See?
감사합니다, 안녕히 계세요
Merci. Au revoir.
[Thanks. Goodbye.]
Tout de la fruit.
에마 잠들었어
Emma's down for the night.
Oh, good.
So I guess I'm going to take off.
나도 이만 가볼게
Okay. Hey, listen, just before you go.
그래... 가기 전에...
Again, I just want to say thank you for coming with me.
이번에 나랑 같이 가줘서 고마워
아냐, 천만에
Oh, no problem.
그리고 네가 한 말 생각해봤는데...
And also, you know, I, uh, I was thinking about what you said, you know,
있잖아, 섹스 안하는 거...
about the whole sex thing, and...
아마도 다시 그 과정을 겪지않는 게
더 좋은 걸지도 모르겠어
probably not a great idea to go down that road again.
그래, 같은 생각이라니 다행이네
Thank you. I'm glad, I'm glad you agree.
아쉽지, 그래도 좋았을 땐
끝내줬었는데
It's a shame, though. I mean, when we did it,
it was pretty good.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
맞는 말이야
Hey, do you remember that one really great time?
그 때, 기억해?
정말 죽였는데
Oh, yeah.
당연하지
You know, it was your birthday.
/ Valentine's day.
- 네 생일날
- 발렌타인데이였지?
아~ 맞아
Oh, yeah.
Well, I guess that's all in the past now.
이제 다 과거지, 뭐
그래
Hmmm-mmmm.
앞으론 절대
Not even one more time?
단 한번도
Not even once.
아무리 간절히 원해도
No matter how much we want it.
제 아무리 절실히 원해도
Even if we want it really bad.
That's what we decided.
우리가 결정한 거니까
Uhm, right!
응... 그래
힘들지 않을까?
It's kinda hard though!
응... 응!
Yeah.
You know, when two people have a connection, you know,
두 사람이 그렇게
서로 연결되어 있는데
that's... just seems like
such a... waste.
꼭... 낭비 같잖아
난 낭비 싫어해
...I hate waste.
로스
Ross?
응
Yes?
이것만 알아둬
Just so you know...
우리 사이에
With us...
절대 '물 건너간' 건 없어
it's never off the table.
젠장, 절대 물 건너가질 않네
Damn it. It's never off the table.
탭댄스 출 줄 알아?
Okay, can you really tapdance?
아니
No.
이력서에서 삭제
It's off the resume.
양궁?
Archery?
아니
No.
승마?
Horseback riding?
무지 많이 떨어지겠지
Would fall off a lot.
10초 안에 우유 1갤런 마시기?
You can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
그건 할 수 있어
That I can do.
우유 1갤런을 10초 안에
마실 수 있다고?
Come on! You can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
All right, watch me!
직접 보여주지
시간 재
준비됐어?
Okay, you time me. Ready?
준비~
Ready...
시작!
GO!
성공!!
You did it!